=Afterlife of Love and Revenge= =Episode 17=
= الآخرة من الحب والانتقام = = الحلقة 17 =
Hold it right there!
امسكها هناك!
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
I'm Mr. Chu's servant.
أنا خادم السيد تشو.
Surely I'm looking for Mr. Chu.
بالتأكيد أنا أبحث عن السيد تشو.
Mr. Chu is being with Miss Qiaoyan.
السيد تشو يجري مع الآنسة كياويان.
Who are you to go disturb them?
من أنت لتذهب لتزعجهم؟
Brush the manure bucket.
نظف دلو السماد بالفرشاة.
Do I need to brush it so clean
هل أحتاج إلى تنظيفه بالفرشاة
for you use it as bowl to eat?
هل تستخدمه كوعاء للأكل؟
How dare you talk back?
كيف تجرؤ على التحدث؟
You...
أنت...
Mr. Chu,
السيد.  تشو
this servant is rude.
هذا العبد وقح.
I'm disciplining her for you.
أنا أقوم بتأديبها من أجلك.
Madam Zhang, you're right.
سيدتي تشانغ ، أنت محقة.
She doesn't seem like she can do any chores.
لا يبدو أنها تستطيع القيام بأي أعمال منزلية.
She doesn't know how a clean thing looks like,
إنها لا تعرف كيف يبدو الشيء النظيف ،
that's why she was quibbling.
لهذا كانت تتجادل.
Why not
لما لا
you show her, Madam Zhang?
أريها سيدتي تشانغ؟
Look carefully.
انظر بحذر.
Great!
رائعة!
Madam Zhang can brush it so well.
سيدتي تشانغ يمكنها تنظيفها جيدًا.
I'm worried for others to handle this.
أنا قلق من أن يتعامل الآخرون مع هذا.
Madam Zhang, I'll let you do this from now on.
سيدتي تشانغ ، سأدعك تفعل هذا من الآن فصاعدًا.
Okay.
تمام.
This is weird.
هذا غريب.
What's Chu Yuzhi's relationship
ما علاقة Chu Yuzhi
with that servant?
مع ذلك العبد؟
This is not right.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
Li Qingmu, come out here! Where are you?
لي تشينغمو ، تعال إلى هنا!  أين أنت؟
Dear, are you looking for me?
عزيزي هل تبحث عني؟
Who are you calling?
من تنادي؟
I think Miss Qiaoyan looks more like your wife.
أعتقد أن الآنسة Qiaoyan تبدو مثل زوجتك.
I shall look for her then.
سأبحث عنها بعد ذلك.
I dare you.
أتحداكم.
My wife is angry.
زوجتي غاضبة.
I wonder how you'll stop being angry?
أتساءل كيف ستتوقف عن الغضب؟
I'm not angry.
انا لست غاضبا.
You've finally admitted that you're my wife.
لقد اعترفت أخيرًا أنك زوجتي.
I dare you to do that again.
أتحداك أن تفعل ذلك مرة أخرى.
Now, things have become like this.
الآن ، أصبحت الأمور على هذا النحو.
I wonder what we should do next.
أتساءل ماذا يجب أن نفعل بعد ذلك.
We can only take one step at a time
لا يمكننا إلا أن نخطو خطوة واحدة في كل مرة
and plan slowly.
والتخطيط ببطء.
But,
ولكن،
you must not push me away anymore.
يجب ألا تدفعني بعيدًا بعد الآن.
Otherwise, something bad might happen.
خلاف ذلك ، قد يحدث شيء سيء.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
If we stop being intimate,
إذا توقفنا عن الحميمية ،
I'm afraid I'd forget who my wife is.
أخشى أن أنسى من هي زوجتي.
You're good.
أنت جيدة أو أنت طيب.
Say it again
قلها ثانية
and I'll pinch you.
وسأقرصك.
I was wrong.
كنت مخطئا.
Sir, I told you to
سيدي ، لقد أخبرتك بذلك
be careful when you eat.
كن حذرا عندما تأكل.
Mr. Qi is here.
السيد تشي هنا.
I'll leave you both.
سأترك كلاكما.
I'm leaving now.
انا راحل الان.
You two...
أنت أيضا...
(It's all Qing Jingyu's fault.)
(كل ذلك خطأ تشينغ جينغ يو).
(If it wasn't for him,)
(إذا لم يكن له ،)
(Qingmu will not impersonate Chu Yuzhi)
(لن تنتحل Qingmu شخصية Chu Yuzhi)
(and I don't have to stay at this place.)
(ولست مضطرًا للبقاء في هذا المكان.)
Madam Zhang,
سيدتي تشانغ ،
your new clothes are nice.
ملابسك الجديدة جميلة.
The material is obviously the premium coloured brocade.
من الواضح أن المادة هي الديباج الملون المتميز.
Of course.
بالطبع.
This is given to me by Miss Qiaoyan.
أعطاني هذا من الآنسة Qiaoyan.
I've
لدي
made the latest design.
صنع أحدث تصميم.
We need to wear decently to work.
نحن بحاجة لارتداء لائق للعمل.
Unlike someone
على عكس شخص ما
who is wearing a torn dress.
من يرتدي فستان ممزق.
I thought she's begging for food in the street.
اعتقدت أنها تتسول للحصول على الطعام في الشارع.
This material is the tribute from the western region.
هذه المادة هي تكريم من المنطقة الغربية.
Not everyone knows how to appreciate it.
لا يعرف الجميع كيف يقدرها.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Longyue,
لونجيوي ،
Mr. Chu is looking for you.
السيد تشو يبحث عنك.
Okay.
تمام.
You don't say.
لا تقل ذلك.
Her dress really looks unique.
فستانها يبدو فريدًا حقًا.
What's unique?
ما هو الفريد؟
Get back to work.
عد الى العمل.
Yes.
نعم.
What?
ماذا؟
You missed me for not seeing me for half a day?
اشتقت لي لعدم رؤيتي لمدة نصف يوم؟
♪You're the fated love coming from the immortal world♪
أنت الحب المقدّر الآتي من العالم الخالد
♪You tie the red strings on the tips of my fingers♪
♪ تقوم بربط الخيوط الحمراء على أطراف أصابعي ♪
♪My heart won't change even if time passes♪
♪ قلبي لن يتغير حتى لو مر الوقت
♪I'll wait for the love in the old place as promised♪
♪ سأنتظر الحب في المكان القديم كما وعدت ♪